[{"answer": "Oh, you know the sex of the baby? Oh, oh oh oh", "docId": "112towdl.htm.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "No, no, no, no, no, I don't want to know, absolutely not. I think, you know, I think you should know until you look down there, and say, oop, there it is!  Or isn't..", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "my friend..", "docId": "112towdl.htm.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Yes, we did, everything's ", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Ok, so it's just because it was my table, I have to buy a new one", "docId": "112towdl.htm.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "What rule? There's no rule, if anything, you owe me a table", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Well, it's a bi", "docId": "112towdl.htm.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "I'm not moving out", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Why, are you moving out", "docId": "112towdl.htm.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "You'd tell me if you were moving out righ", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "So what are you gonna do", "docId": "112towdl.htm.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Oh, yeah, you have to tell her", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "I don't know...right, he's the pig", "docId": "112towdl.htm.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Oh, God, he's such a pig", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Such a pig", "docId": "112towdl.htm.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Oh he's like a..", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Oh, God, he's such a pig", "docId": "112towdl.htm.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "He's like a big disgusting..", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Oh he's like a..", "docId": "112towdl.htm.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "...like a..", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "You all right", "docId": "112towdl.htm.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Come here.  Listen, you deserve so much better than him...you know, I mean, you, you, you should be with a guy who knows what he has when he has you", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "No. I just need to be by myself for a while, you know? I just got to figure out what I wan", "docId": "112towdl.htm.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "No, I know, I know, and I'm sure your little boy is not going to grow up to be one. ROSS", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "112towdl.htm.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Uh...no. No, no, in fact, you're not having a boy", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "", "docId": "112towdl.htm.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Wh", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Wh", "docId": "112towdl.htm.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "I'm having a boy! Oh, I'm having a boy", "qsentId": 30}]